本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
今晚的最后一个魔术
For tonight's final illusion
让我们来看这个难以置信的神秘袋子
we have incredible sack of mystery.
当你把钱放进去后  财富就会神奇的不翼而飞啦
When you put your money in, it mysteriously dissapears.
当然了  多有道理啊
Well, of course! That makes perfect sense!
多好的人啊  这太值得一试了
What a nice man! That was totaly worth a try!
这只老虎在爆炸中受了重伤
The tiger was badly injured in the explosion
但是我们给它安装了一个拳头
but we repaired him with a fist.
哇塞  这只老虎是我们的英雄
Woo! Yeah! That tiger is our hero!
猛虎之拳  广告之后马上回来
Tiger fist! will return after these messages.
快看  这就是我和你们说的那个广告
Hey look! It's that commercial I've been telling you guys about.
你是否一筹莫展  憔悴苦楚
Are you completely miserable?
就是啊
Yeees!
那你需要去见一下吉迪恩
Then you need to meet Gideon.
-吉迪恩  -他有什么特别之处
- Gideon? - What makes him so special?
他是个通灵者
He's a psychic!
所以不要浪费你们的时间  和那些自诩神秘之人厮混
So don't waste your time with other so called man of mystery.
明天  今晚就来吉迪恩的通灵帐篷中了解详情吧
Learn about it tomorrow, tonight, at Gideon's tent of telepathy!
警告：本广告在禁止地区无效，不接受货到付款，通灵中的“灵”字不发音且仅用于娱乐目的。如不满意，请退回未使用的部分以领取全额退款。副作用包括但不限于：兴旺发达、大量现金、聚会尽兴、紧身裤、年增长6.2%、不用按揭！
通灵读物可能导致腹部突然发热。如果疼痛持续，请立即咨询你的物理学家。卡拉，我一直很爱你但就是没胆量说出来。
我开始好奇里面有什么了
I'm getting all curiousy inside.
好奇害死猫
Well don't get too curiousy,
自从那个吉迪恩怪物来这儿之后  就尽给我惹麻烦
Ever since that monster Gideon rolled in town, I've had nothing but trouble.
吉迪恩
Gideon!
-他真的是个疯子吗  -我觉得咱们可以去一探究竟
- Well, is he realy psychic? - I think we should go and find out!
做梦  不允许你们让这场竞争升级
Never! You're forbiden from patronizing the competition!
住在我屋檐下的人可不允许到吉迪恩的屋檐下去
No one that lives under my roof is allowed under that Gideon's roof.
-帐篷有屋檐吗  -我觉得咱们找到漏洞了  字面上的漏洞
- Do tents have roofs? - I think we just found our loophole. Literaly.
所以快来吧  伙计们  吉迪恩正翘首以待
So come down soon, folks. Gideon is expecting you.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
■
翻译： 蝉君
校订： WaitinZ
■
后期： WaitinZ  liloelva
怪诞小镇  第一季第四集
Gravity Falls  S01E04  The hand that rocks Mabel
伙计们  到这儿来  快把你们的钱放进吉迪恩的神秘袋子
Get right here folks! Put your money in Gideon's psychick sack!
当然  哇塞  太有道理了
Oh sure! Wow! That makes perfect sense!
这就像是神秘小屋的奇怪翻版
Aww, this is like a bizzaro version of the Mystery Shack.
他们甚至还有自己的苏斯
They even have their own Soos.
要开始了  要开始了
It's starting, it's starting!
让咱们瞧瞧这怪物的庐山真面目
Let's see what this monster looks like.
好啊美国人  我叫小吉迪恩
Hello America! My name is Lil' Gideon!
这就是斯坦叔公的不共戴天之敌吗
That's Stan's mortal enemy?
他还真是  够娇小的啊
Like.. he's so.. widdle.
女士们先生们  你们赏光莅临此处真是天赐珍宝啊
Ladies and gentlemen, it is such a gift to have you here tonight.
珍宝啊  我看见了一个景象
Such a gift. I have a vision.
我预计  你们不久就会说
I predict, you'll soon all say..
-成真了  -什么  我并不觉得多稀奇啊
- It came true! - What? I'm not impresed.
你明明被震撼到了
You're impresed!
音乐起  老爸
Hit it dad!
哦  我能看见  别人所无法瞧见的东西
Oh I can see, what others can't see!
这并不是什么老把戏  那只是变幻莫测
It ain't some such old trick, it's an natability.
别人将一切置若罔闻  我却倾向于未来之景
Where others are blind, I am futurely inclined.
而你们也得享我所见之物
and you too could see the view that's widdle lil me!
来吧  每个人  集中起来  我想听你们接着唱下去
Come on everybody! Round up! I want you all to keep it going!
-什么  他怎么做到的  -继续唱
- What? How did he? - Keep it going!
-你希望儿子多唤声你  -我给了猫咪所有的一切
- You wish your son would call you more! - I'm leaving everything to my cats!
-我看见你们曾来过此处  -是什么让我露了馅
- I sense that you've been here before! - What gave it away?
得了吧
Come on.
如果可以的话  我要读透你的心
I'll read your mind if I'm able
-直觉告诉我  你的名字叫梅宝  -这太神了
- Something tells me your name Mabel. - How he do that?
欢迎你们
So welcome all yeeee
来到通灵帐篷
to the tent of telepathy
感谢你们来见小小的我
and thanks for visiting widdle ol' meee
噢  我的天哪
Oh my goodness.
谢谢你们  你们才是真正的奇迹
Thank you! You people are the real miracles.
天呐  这小鬼比斯坦叔公还要会鬼扯
Man, this kid is even bigger fraud than Stan.
-怪不得叔公会嫉妒  -那是  他的舞姿真是太可爱了
- No wonder our uncle is jealous. - Oh come on, his dance moves were adorable
还有  你瞧见他的头发了吗  太潮了啊
And did you see his hair? It was like wooosh.
-你真容易被打动  -是啦  是啦
- You're too easily impressed - Yeah, yeah.
迪普快看  我成功地给我的脸镶钻了
Check it out Dipper! I succesfuly bezappled my face!
-这是永久性的吗  -我正在享受有限的时间
- Is that permanent? - I'm on appreciating my time.
-谁来开开门啊  -我来了
- Somebody answer that door! - I'll get it!
-你好啊  -是小小的你
- Howdy? - It's widdle old you!
我知道我的歌声挺朗朗上口的
Yeah, my song is quite catchy.
我们虽然没有正式见过面
I know we haven't formaly met.
但昨天表演之后  你的笑声就萦绕在我的脑海里
but after yesterday's perfomance, I just couldn't get your laugh out of my head.
你说这样笑
You mean this one?
太愉悦了  当我在观众中瞧见你  我就对自己说
Aw, what a delight. And when I saw you in the audience, I said to myself
我找到了相似的灵魂
now, there is a kindred spirit.
喜欢闪闪发亮的东西还爱笑的人
Someone who appreciates sparkly things and laugh.
就是说我啊
That's totally me!
迷人啊  真是太迷人了
Enchanting. Utterly enchanting.
-谁在门口  -没人  斯坦叔公
- Who's at the door? - No one Grunkle Stan!
感谢你的谨慎行事  斯坦那家伙可不待见我
I appreciate your discretion, that Stan is no fan of mine.
真没想到那种烂柠檬竟然也会有你这样的甜心蜜桃相伴
I don't know how a lemon so sour could be related to a peach so sweet.
-吉迪恩  -你觉得
- Gideon! - What do you say,
我们离开这儿  再谈点别的
we step away from here and chat a bit more.
比如在我的化妆室里面谈谈怎么样
Perhaps in my dressing room?
化妆啊
Makeovers!
你瞧见什么中意了的吗  我瞧见了
Do you see something you like? Cause I do..
什么
What?
迪普  看看发生什么了
Hey Dipper! What's going on?
你去哪里了  还有你的手指甲又怎么了
Where have you been? And what's going on with
看上去就像黄鼠狼
those finger nails, you look like a wolverine.
我知道  不错吧  哈哈
I know, right? Waaa!
我和我的新伙计吉迪恩出去了  他可真是个浓缩的精华啊
I'm hanging out with my new pal Gideon. He's one dapper little man.
梅宝  我可不相信发型会大过脑袋的家伙
Mabel, I don't trust anyone who's hair is bigger than their head.
算了吧  你根本不想陪我做些女孩的事情
Aw, leave him alone. You never wanna do girly stuff with me.
你和苏斯净做男孩的事情
You and Soos could do boy stuff all the time.
-你说什么  -伙计
- What do you mean? - Hey dude.
-你准备好来用微波炉一根一根炸热狗了吗  -当然
- You ready to blow up these hotdogs in a microwave one by one? - Am I?
一次一根  一次一根
One at a time! One at a time!
哇  从你家工厂这儿望去的景色真是太棒了
Wow! The view from your family factory is nuts!
好在我们带了剧场观望眼镜
Good thing we both brought our opera glasses!
梅宝  当我身处这里  俯视着这些小可怜们
Mabel, when I'm up here looking down on all them lil old people.
我就觉得我是目及一切的王者
I feel like I'm king of all I survey.
-而你就是当之无愧的女王  -什么
- And guess that makes you my queen! - What?
你这样对我真好
You've being so nice to me right now.
快别这样了
Quit it!
我无法停止  因为我用自己的内心诉说
I can't quit it. I'm speaking from my heart.
-用哪儿呢  -梅宝  我从未感到和人这么亲近
- From the where now? - Mabel, I've never felt this close to anyone.
如此  如此亲近
So..so close.
吉迪恩  听着  我
Look Gideon, I am ..
我挺喜欢你的  但是我们还是只做朋友吧
I like you a lot but let's just be friends.
至少给我个机会吧  梅宝  你能够给我这个荣幸
At least give me a chance. Mabel, will you do me the honour
-邀请你和我约会吗  -游戏约会
- of going on a date with me? - A play date?
购物约会
A shopping date?
这只是个小小的约会
It will just be one lil old date.
我对我的扣式领带发誓
I swear with my lucky bolo tie.
好吧  我想
Okay, then. I guess.
梅宝・派恩斯  你让我成为了世界上最幸福的人
Mable Pines, you have made me the happiest boy in the world.
你在嗅我的头发吗
Are you sniffing my hair?
这可不是约会  迪普  你知道那只是
It's not a date, Dip, it's just, you know
我不想伤害他的感情  等他想明白了  我就给他点安慰
I didn't want to hurt his feelings. Until he figured it, I'd throw him a bone.
梅宝  男孩子可不是这么想的  他会坠入爱河的
Mabel, guys don't work that way. He's gonna fall in love with you.
噗  你说个鬼啦
Pff, yeah, right.
我还没有这么招人喜爱呢
I'm not THAT lovable.
-秒杀你  -好吧  咱们还是达成了一点点共识
- Kaboom! Yes! - Okay, at least we agree on something here.
一个神奇的夜晚等着咱们呢  我的女士
A night of enchantment awaits, my lady.
哦天
Oh boy.
不敢相信他们竟然允许带马进来
I can't believe they'd let us bring horse in here.
人们都不忍心对我说“不”
Well, people have hard time saying 'no' to me.
吉迪恩先生  把脚搁在桌子上
Ah! Monsieur Gideon! The feet on the table!
有创意
An excellent choice!
-让-吕克  咱们本来是怎么说的来着  -对对  您说的对
- Jean-Luc, what have we discussed about our contact? - Yes, yes. Very good.
我从没有看见过这么多人
I've never seen so many forks.
还有带泡泡的水  太赞了
And water with bubbles in it? Oh, ulala, weewee.
哦  你会说法语吗
Oh, parlez-vous francais?
我听不懂你在说什么
I have no idea what you're saying.
报纸上面梅宝怎么会和
Hey, hey! What the jackal is Mabel doing
那个疯狂的豺狼吉迪恩在一起
in the paper next to that crazy pitpocket Gideon?
这可是个轰动新闻
Oh, yeah. That's like a big deal.
每个人都在谈论吉迪恩和梅宝今晚的约会
Everybody's talking about Gideon and Mabel's big date tonight.
什么  那个奸诈小人竟然在和我的完美侄孙女约会
What? That little shyster is dating my great niece?
我在想这对强强组合会有什么新名字
I wonder what the new name will be for the power couple?
梅迪恩  吉迪宝  梅吉宝迪恩
Mabidion? Gidiable? Magidbelion!
我不知道  我没听说过  而且  我让她别接近那个家伙了
I didn't know! I didn't hear about it! And plus, I told her not to!
今晚一切都会终结  我立马就去那个讨厌鬼的家里
Yeah, well it ends tonight. I'm going right down to that little scug's house.
一切马上就会结束
This is gonna stop right now.
伙计  如果那是个壁橱该有多可笑啊
Dude, woudn't it be funny if that was a closet?
他就不得不折回来  重走一遍真正的大门
And he had to come back again and walk through the real door?
唉哟  是真的门
Nope, real door.
吉迪恩  你这个小混球  快开门
Gideon, you little punk! Open up!
我可不会重复第二次
I will pardon nothing!
怎么  斯坦・派恩斯
Why! Stan Pines!
-多荣幸啊  -别挡路  伙计
- What a delight! - Out of the way, bud.
我在找吉迪恩
I'm looking for Gideon.
我没看见那小家伙  不过既然你来这儿了
Well, I haven't seen the boy around, but since you're here.
不如进屋来喝杯咖啡吧
You simply must come in for coffee.
-但我是为了  -进口货色哦  从哥伦比亚运过来的
- Bu but I came.. - It's imported. All the way from Columbia.
我在那儿蹲过一次监狱
I went to jail there once.
你这儿好东西还不少
Some digs you got here.
这件  这件太漂亮了
Oh, this. This is beautiful.
我听说你的侄孙女和我的吉迪恩
Now, I hear your niece and my Gideon are well,
可以说  正在度过琴瑟和鸣的晚上呢
they are singing in harmony lately, so to speak.
我可是大大反对的
Yeah, and I'm against it.
不不不  我觉得这可是一个很好的商机
No, no, no. I see it as a fantastic business oportunity.
没错  神秘小屋和通灵帐篷
Yes, the Mystery Shack and the Tent of Telepathy.
我们互相攻击了这么久了  让我拿掉这个
We'd been at each other's throats for far.. Let me get that.
实在是互相攻讦太久太过了  不是吗
At each others throats for far too long, yes we have.
是时候让我们冰释前嫌了
This is our big chance to brush aside our rivalry
我们共挖一桶金的时刻来了
and pull our collective profit, you see.
你继续说
I'm listening.
然后我说  自己在你脑门上签名吧  小姑娘
So I said, autograph your own head, shot lady!
梅宝  今晚的约会实在太成功了
Mabel, tonight's date was a complete success.
我保证明天的约会会更上一层楼的
And tomorrow's date promises to top this one in every way!
停下  你说过只有一次约会  而这就是最后一次
Woah, woah. You said just one date and this was it.
多棒的惊喜啊  一个红冠南美鹦鹉
What a surprise! A red-crested South American rainbow maco!
二  三  四
Two.. three.. four..
梅宝  你  愿意  陪伴  吉迪恩
Mabel! Will! You! Accompany! Gideon!
在  周柿  去  舞厅  跳舞  吗
To! The ballroom! Dance! This! Thurpsday!
周四
Thursday!
-太可爱了  -吉迪恩有女朋友了
- Oh so adorable. - Gideon got a girlfriend.
他们都期待着呢  请答应我吧
They're expecting us, please say you'll go.
吉迪恩  我很抱歉我要说
Gideon, I'm sorry but I'm gonna have to say..
-我紧张得都要坐不住了  -这太甜蜜了
- I'm on the edge of my seat - This is gonna be adorable.
如果她拒绝了  我会伤心而死的
If she says no, I'll die from sadness.
我能证明这真的可能发生
I can verify that will indeed happen.
嘿  约会情况怎样
Hey! How did it go?
我不知道  我有了只龙虾
I don't know.. I have a lobster now..
没事  反正一切都结束了  你也不用再和他约会了
Well, at least it's over and you will never have to go out with him again.
梅宝  一切是结束了吧
Mabel, it's over, right?
梅宝
Mabel?
他又约我出去了  我不知道该怎么拒绝
He asked me out again and I didn't know how to say NO!
就像这样  我不要
Like this - NO.
事情并不是这么简单的  迪普
It's not that easy, Dipper.
我是喜欢吉迪恩  但这是像对朋友和哥哥的那种喜欢
I do like Gideon, as a friend/little sister.
我不想伤害他的感情
So I didn't want to hurt his feelings.
我只想让一切复归原位
I just need to get things back where they used to be.
你知道的  朋友的状态
You know, friends.
划船之夜  划船之夜
Boat midnight, boat midnight.
你知道吗  我本以为跳舞就是这个晚上的结尾了
You know, I thought dancing would be the end of the evening, right?
你难道不想让这一刻能永存吗  亲爱的
Don't you want this evening to last my sweet?
不  我是说  是的  我的意思是  我很开心能和朋友在一起
NO! I mean, yes. I mean, I'm always happy hanging with a friend.
伙伴  伙计  友人  所有可以描述朋友的词语
Buddy, pal, chump, other word for friend.
-伙计  -我说过这个词了  比如伴侣
- Pal? - I already said pal. A mate?
灵魂伴侣吗
How about soulmate?
这可真是无法拒绝啊
Well, you can't say no to that.
他这人挺好  但是我不能再继续下去了
He's so nice, but I can't keep doing this.
但我又不能伤了他的心  救命啊  没有活路了
But I can't break his heart. Aaah! I have no way out!
约会的时候究竟又发生了什么
What in the heck happened on that date?
我不知道  我是想保持在友情区域的
I don't know. I was in the friend-zone
但等到我回过神来  他已经把我拉到浪漫区域了
and then before I knew what was happening, he pulled me into romance zone!
这就像个陷阱  危险的陷阱
It was like quicksand! Geopardy quicksand!
梅宝  算了吧  你又不是要嫁给吉迪恩
Mabel, come on. It's not like you'll have to marry Gideon.
好消息  梅宝  你得嫁给吉迪恩
Great news, Mabel. You have to marry Gideon.
-什么  -这是我和战略伙伴格里佛的计划的一部分
- What? - It's all a part of my long-term deal with buddy Gleafall.
这事儿涉及到很多的钱  而且我还捞了这件衬衫
There's a lot of cash tied up in this thing, plus I got this shirt.
我太胖了
I am fat.
修身啊  亲爱的  修身
Bodies change, honey! Bodies change.
-梅宝  -梅宝不在这儿
- Oh no, Mabel. - Mabel's not here.
-她在汗衫城呢  -那你准备从汗衫城出来吗
- She's in sweater town. - Are you gonna come out of sweater town?
好了  我看不下去了
All right. Enough is enough.
-如果你难以跟吉迪恩分手  我帮你去说  -真的吗
- If you can't break up with Gideon, than I'll do it for you. - You will?
-太谢谢你了  谢谢  谢谢  -没事儿
- Oh thank you, thank you, thank you - Allright, allright.
你好  迪普・派恩斯  过得如何
Hello! Dipper Pines, how are you?
-你看上去挺精神的  -谢谢  你也
- You look good, you look good. - Thanks, you are..
吉迪恩  我们得谈谈  梅宝今晚不来了
Look, Gideon. We've gotta talk. Mabel isn't joining you tonight.
她不想再看见你了
She doesn't want to see you anymore.
毫无冒犯之意  但她有点儿被你吓坏了
She's kinda weirded out by you, no offense.
所以你是要表达
So what you're saying is..
-你要阻碍我们  -你是要
- You've come between us. - You're not gonna like
发飙了还是怎么的啊
freak out or anything, are you?
当然不会  这也是会发生的事情嘛
Of course not. This things happen.
不错  那么  真是抱歉了  伙计  不过
So, okay cool. Well, then again, sorry man, but uh..
嘿  振作起来
Hey, thumbs up!
振作起来  确实是这样  我的好朋友
Thumbs up, indeed my friend.
怎么样  他生气了吗
How did it go? Was he mad?
他又用那神秘的力量来探测你的想法了吗
Did he try to read your mind with his psychic powers?
别担心  梅宝  他只是个孩子  他可没有什么力量
Don't worry Mable, he's just a kid. He doesn't have any powers.
迪普・派恩斯  你不明白自己究竟做了什么
Dipper Pines, you don't know what you've done.
你刚刚犯了自己一生中最大的错误
You've just made the biggest mistake of your life.
吉迪恩・查理斯・格里佛  立马给我收拾干净你的房间
Gideon Charles Gleafall, clean up your room this instant.
我可以把你买来再卖掉  老家伙
I can buy and sell you old man!
有道理
Fair enough.
打我吧  伙计
Hit me dude!
-感觉不错  -我很高兴一切回到正轨了
- Feels good. - I'm so glad everything's back to normal.
-你接电话  -你接  哦  算了
- Your turn. - Your tur.. Aw, man.
-你好  -我是托比・迪特敏德  重力泉八卦报
- Hello? - Toby Determined, Gravity Falls Gossiper.
你好  上周指控你参与谋杀案的事很抱歉
Oh, hey man. Sorry for acusing you of murder last week.
都过去的事情了嘛  那个
Water under the bridge. Saay..
我们想要采访你  自从你来到这儿
We want to interview you about whether you've seen anything
是否看见过什么奇妙的东西
unusual in tihs hiertown ever since you've arrived.
终于啊  我还以为没人会问呢
Oh! Finally! I thought nobody would ever ask!
我有笔记和理论
I have notes and theories! Aha..
地鼠路412号  今晚见吗
412 Gopher road. Tonight?
-明白了  -好了  我做完你交代的任务了
- Got it. - There! I did your dirty work.
现在该你支付酬劳了
Now it's time to pay your end of the bargain.
珊多拉・西梅内斯的电话号码
Shandra Jimenez's phone number!
上帝保佑你  吉迪恩
Bless you, lil Gideon!
你好
Hello!
朋友你好
Hello friend.
-吉迪恩  -迪普・派恩斯
- Gideon. - Dipper Pines.
你来这个城市有多久了  一周  两周
How long have you been living in this town? A week? Two?
你喜欢这儿么  享受这番景致吗
You like it here? Enjoy the scenery?
-你究竟想要干什么  -仔细给我听好了
- What do you want from me, man? - Listen carefully boy.
这个城市有你压根儿无法理解的秘密
This town has secrets you couldn't begin to comprehend.
是因为梅宝吗  我和你说过了  她不喜欢你
Is this about Mabel? I told you, she's not into you.
骗子  是你挑拨了我们
Liar! You turned her agains me!
她是我的水蜜桃饺子
She was my peach dumpling!
你没事吧  伙计
Are you okay man?
你好
Howdy!
我不仅仅会读懂别人的心
Reading minds isn't all I can do.
但是  你不是假冒的吗
But... but you're a fake..
那你告诉我  迪普  这也是假冒的吗
Oh, tell me Dipper. Is this fake?
你的头发尝起来如何  伙计
How's your hair tasting buddy?
温蒂  我需要点建议
Wendy, I need some advice.
-你和人分手过吧  -当然
- You've broken up with guys, right? - Oh yeah.
拉斯・托曼  伊莱・霍尔  史托尼・戴维森
Russ Toram, Eli Hall, Stoney Davidson.
我不知道是哪里不对劲
I don't know what's wrong with me.
我本以为一切都已经正常了  但我仍然觉得不舒服
I thought everytrhing was back to normal, but I still feel all gross.
弗雷克・屋利  内特・霍尔斯  哦  还有个纹身的家伙
Flake Wurly,  Nate Halls, oh, the guy with the tattoos.
或许让迪普帮我是错误的
Maybe letting Dipper do it for me was a mistake.
我得自己同吉迪恩好好说分手的事儿
Gideon deserves an honest break up
迪恩尼・费尔德曼  马克・埃普斯丁
Deanny Feldman, Mark Epstin, oh.
天呐  我还不确定自己是否和他分手了呢
Oh man, I'm not sure I actualy broke up with him.
怪不得他一直给我打电话
No wonder he keeps calling me.
我知道我该怎么办了  谢谢你和我聊天  温蒂
I know what I gotta do. Thatnls for talking to me, Wendy.
忽略
Ignore.
斯坦叔公说的对  你就是个怪物
Grunkle Stan was right about you! You are a monster!
你姐姐是我的了
Your sister will be mine!
-谁是那可爱的小甜心  是你  -不  是你
- Who's the cute little guy? You are! - No you are!
-她是不会和你约会的  -骗人的
- She's never gonna date you, man! - That's a lie!
朋友  我要让你再也不能对我撒谎
And I'm gonna make sure you never lie to me again, friend.
吉迪恩  我们得谈谈
Gideon! We have to talk!
梅宝  我的棉花糖  你在这儿干嘛
Mabel! My marshmallow! What are you doing here?
吉迪恩  我很抱歉  但我不是你的棉花糖
I'm sorry Gideon, but I can't be your marshmallow.
我来这儿是为了跟你说实话
I am here to be honest and tell you that myself.
我  我不明白
I..I don't understand.
梅宝  现在或许不是吐露真心话的最好时机
Mabel, this probably isn't the best time to be brutaly honest with him!
但是我们仍然能够做好朋友的  不是吗
Hey, but we can still be makeover buddies, right?
-你不喜欢这样吗  -真的吗
- Woudn't you like that? - Really?
不  当然是假的
No! Not really!
你竟然袭击我弟弟  发什么神经啊
You were like attacking my brother! What the heck?
我的领带  快还给我
My tie! Give it back!
没了这个  你就一筹莫展了吧
Not so powerfull without this, are you?
迪普
Dipper!
吉迪恩你听着  我们完了  我不会再和你约会了
Listen Gideon. It's over. I will never ever date you.
棒
Yeah!
我的力量
My powers!
这不算完  这不会是你最后一次看见我
Oh, this isn't over. This isn't the last you'll see of lil..ol..me.
这才是生活  兄弟
This is living brother.
从现在开始  你就吃品牌食品  欣赏小丑画像吧
From now on, it's all named brand foods and clown paintings.
-吉迪恩  你看  -斯坦佛・派恩斯
-  Well hehey Gideon, look what.. - Stanpher Pines!
我指责你们  我指责你们
I rebuke thee! I rebuke thee!
指责  这是个词吗
Rebuke? Is that a word?
派恩斯家族已经把我给惹毛了
The entire Pines family have invoked my fury!
你们会为自己的僭越付出代价的
You will all pay recompense for you transgressions!
怎么  你是有了个一天一词的日历  还是别的什么
What, you got like a word-a-day calendar or something?
不过阳光男孩  我们和梅宝的联姻怎么办啊
B-but-but but sunshine, what about our arrangement with Mable and..
闭嘴
Silence!
我看他是又生气了
Well, I see he's taking one of his rages again.
抱歉  斯坦  我得和吉迪恩站在同一战线上
Sorry, Stan. I'll have to stand with Gideon on this one.
行行  我知道自己是不受欢迎的客人了
Okay, okay. I can see when I'm not wanted.
斯坦  我很抱歉  不过我得要回这幅画  斯坦
Stan, I'm sorry, but I'm gonna need that painting back, Staaan!
斯坦
Stan!
有本事来抓我啊  傻帽
Try and catch me, suckers!
我本可以拥有一切
I could've had it all.
你们两个究竟干了什么好事
What the heck happened to you two?
-吉迪恩  -吉迪恩
- Gideon. - Gideon.
吉迪恩
Gideon.
那个怪胎可是扬言要向我们家族复仇呢
Yeah, the little mutant swore vengeance on the whole family.
看来他是要咬我的后脚跟之类的了
I guess he's gonna nibble my anckles or something.
就是就是  放马过来吧  看他准备怎么打击我们
Oh yeah. Yeah! How is he gonna destroy us now, huh?
试着想想看我们在想哪个数字
Try to think what number we're thinking of?
他永远也猜不到我在想哪个数字
He'll never guess what number I'm thinking of.
负数八  没人会想到去猜负数的
Negative 8! Noone would guess a negative number!
当心  有人在谋划摧毁我们的计划了
Oh, look out! Somebody's planning our destruction right now.
吉迪恩  我仍然爱你
Gideon, I still love you.
要是没有家人的阻挠的话
If only my family weren't in the way.
看看我  我又老又臭气熏天的
Look at me. I'm old and I'm smelly.
没了护身符看你还能耍什么威风
Hey, what are you going to do without your precious amulet?
让我们拭目以待吧  朋友
Oh, you'll see boy.
拭目以待
You'll see.
-你好了吗  -还没有
- You're done. - Not yet.
-现在呢  -快了
- How about now? - Almost.
好了
And.. there.
让我们来吧
Let's do this.
你被解雇了
You're fired.